http://www.montest.com/info/privacy-4

Items
(0 Items)
Home
ProductsTest Pattern Generators4K Ultra HD HDMI Video Test Pattern Generator/Analyzer Low-Cost 4K HDMI Video Test Pattern GeneratorHDMI Video Test Pattern GeneratorSignal GeneratorComponent Video Test Pattern GeneratorVGA Video Pattern GeneratorHD-SDI Video Pattern Generator3G-SDI Video Test Pattern GeneratorCCTV TestersProfessional CCTV Tester with Power Over Ethernet (PoE) and IP TestingCCTV Tester with Wrist StrapLED TesterLED TesterVideo SplittersHDMI 1.2 SplitterHDMI 1.3b SplitterVGA Video SplitterDVI/VGA Quad Screen Multiviewer with Built-In KVM SwitchCables & AdaptersVGA CablesStandard VGAVGA Monitor CableVGA Monitor Cables with FerritesSuper Flat VGASuper Flat VGA Extension Cable - Male-to-FemaleSuper Flat VGA Monitor Cable - Male-to-MaleFlat VGAFlat VGA Monitor Cable - Male-to-MaleFlat VGA Extension Cable - Male-to-FemaleUltra Thin VGAUltra Thin VGA Monitor Cable - Male-to-MaleUltra Thin VGA Monitor Cable with Ferrites - Male-to-MaleSuper Thin VGASuper Thin VGA Extension Cable - Male-to-FemaleSuper Thin VGA Monitor Cable - Male-to-MaleThin VGAThin VGA Extension Cable with Gold Connectors & Ferrites - Male-to-FemaleThin VGA Monitor Cable with Gold Connectors & Ferrites - Male-to-MaleDown/Up Angled VGADown Angled to Straight Connector VGA Cable, Male-to-MaleUp Angled to Straight Connector VGA Cable, Male-to-MaleLeft/Right Angled VGA90 Degree Left Angled to Straight Connector VGA Cable, Male-to-Male90 Degree Right Angled to Straight Connector VGA Cable, Male-to-MaleVGA + USB KVMVGA + USB Extension Cable, Male-to-FemaleVGA + USB Interface Cable, Male-to-MaleVGA + PS2 KVMVGA + PS/2 Keyboard & Mouse Extension Cable, Male-to-FemaleHDMI CablesStandard HDMIHDMI Interface CableLong HDMI Interface Cable with Built-in Equalizer, Male-to-Male4K HDMI Active Cables4K HDMI Active Cable with Signal Booster, Male to MaleHDMI with EthernetHDMI with Ethernet Cable, 28 AWG - Male-to-MaleUltra Thin HDMI with Ethernet Cable, 36 AWG - Male-to-MaleType-C Mini HDMIHDMI Type A to Type C Cable, 30 AWG - Male-to-MaleHDMI Type C Interface Cable, 30 AWG - Male-to-MaleDVI to HDMIDVI-I to HDMI-A Interface Cable - Male-to-MaleDVI-I Single Link CablesDVI-I Single Link Interface Cable - Male-to-MaleHDTV Component Video CablesAdapters & Gender ChangersSUN Video Male to VGA Female AdapterDVI-I Male to VGA Female AdapterHDMI Gender Changer, Female-to-FemaleHDMI Gender Changer, Male-to-MaleHDMI Gender Change, Male-to-FemaleHDMI Female to DVI-D Male AdapterHDMI Male to DVI-D Female Adapter. BNC/RCA Composite Video + S-Video to VGA ConverterInformationAbout VPIContact UsPress RoomTechnical ArticlesPrivacy StatementWarranty PolicyAccepted Payments
My AccountLog In / Register
Cart
Quote List
Contact Us
Cart
0
Products
Product
(empty)
No products
$0.00
Shipping
$0.00
Total
Cart Checkout
Products
Test Pattern Generators
Privacy Statement
Video Products Inc believes that our customers are our most valuable assets. We recognize that building a long-term business relationship with you depends on earning your trust, and that respecting and protecting your privacy is part of this commitment. Demonstrating this commitment is one reason we have chosen to participate in the BBBOnLine Privacy Program. We proudly display the BBBOnLine Privacy Seal. We have designed our website so that, in general, you can explore the information offered without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. Once you choose to provide personally identifiable information (name, address, email address, phone number.), you can rest assured that it will only be used to support your relationship with VPI.Please be aware that VPI's privacy practices may vary as required by local laws and policies. Regardless of later updates or changes to our privacy notice, we will never use the information you submit under our current privacy notice in a new way without first providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prevent that use.
We want you to be informed and aware…
This Online Privacy Statement is provided by VPI in order to make you aware of our privacy practices, and of the choices you can make about how information is collected and used. VPI's Online Privacy Statement is available from our homepage and from every page where information is collected. VPI pledges to clearly outline the choices you have when you register for a product or service. At the time of registration, you may choose to opt-out of receiving email from VPI about other products or services. You may also exercise your opt-out choice at any time. For additional information, see the Your Ability to Opt-Out section below.
About what information we collect…
VPI offers our website visitors the opportunity to:
view product information.
request hard copies of our catalogs.
purchase products.
participate in the VPI forum Message Board.
We may ask you to provide personal information in order to process these business transactions efficiently. The information you share with VPI will be used to support the customer relationship you have with VPI.VPI collects visitor information in the following areas:
Use of "Contact Video Products"page.
Use of "Free VPI Catalog"page.
Use of online shopping.
Depending on the type of transaction you request, you may be asked to provide your name, contact and billing information, transaction and credit card information, contact preferences, and email address. Cookies At some of VPI's websites, technologies such as "cookies" may be used to assist in our web traffic analysis. A "cookie" is a piece of text which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. If you agree, then your browser adds the text in a small file.Using cookies helps us give you a better web site to use, by letting us monitor what's working and what isn't through site traffic analysis. This allows us to evaluate and enhance the usefulness of our website, and the ease with which visitors can find the information offered. VPI wants to be sure you understand that accepting a cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any personal information about you, other than that data you chose to share with us.
You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to choose whether to accept it or not. You can delete the files that contain cookies; those files are stored as part of your internet browser. We know that a lot of people have concerns about cookies, but in talking with many of our customers, we believe that the benefit we both gain from their proper use is worthwhile. We value the relationships we have with our customers so we respect these concerns. VPI works to continuously improve the VPI web experience and personal data privacy policy and practices.
How we use the personally identifiable information you provide….
VPI uses the information you provide to better understand your needs and provide you with better service. Specifically, we use your information to:
help you complete the desired transaction.
communicate back to you.
update you regarding products, services and benefits.
adapt our website and printed materials to fit your needs.
Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and are retained in encrypted form only. We may also occasionally use your information to contact you for market research or provide you with marketing information we think would be of particular interest. VPI will always give you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving such contact. In addition, we will also follow local requirements, such as allowing you to opt-in before receiving unsolicited contact, where applicable. Contact information such as products purchased, source of lead, date of first contact and last purchase, and type of information requested, are collected and are linked to personally identifiable information such as name and address in our database. This information is analyzed in a consolidated form to determine future product and advertising initiatives to best serve our customers. Analysis of individual buying behavior may be utilized to grant discounts, or extend lines of credit.
How we ensure the security of the information you provide…
At VPI, we are committed to ensuring the security of your information. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of info, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We use VeriSign encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information. All customer information is kept in data files to which access is limited to only those employees who must use this information to process the order. Access to hard copy paperwork is limited through the use of locked cabinets in our facilities and a security system is also in place to protect our premises. All employees, agents and affiliates of VPI have who might have access to confidential customer information in the conduct of their duties have agreed to hold this information in confidence, not to use it for any purpose except to carry out the service they are providing for our organization, and to honor our privacy and security policies in the way this information is handled. Under no circumstances will we use this information for anything else not described in this privacy policy. VPI's Privacy Advocate is responsible for conducting investigations into any alleged computer or network compromises, incidents or problems and ensuring the proper disciplinary action is taken against those who violate VPI's Information Security Policy. Any security compromises or potential security compromises and any inquiries concerning security should be reported to privacy.advocate@vpi.us.
Information sharing policies…
Certain transactions you may initiate inherently indicate a request to share your information with VPI partners or associates. For instance, when you fill out the contact form to request information from one of our International Distributors, that request will be forwarded to the Distributor in question. If you post to the VPI forum Message Board, other participants will be able to read and respond to that post. Unless we have your permission or are required by law, we will only share the personal data you provide online with business partners who are acting on our behalf for the uses described above. Such business partners are governed by our privacy policies with respect to the use of this data and are bound by the appropriate confidentiality agreements. The information shared with these partners does not include sensitive information such as credit card numbers, credit information, medical information, social security numbers or other related information, nor personally identifiable information regarding children.
VPI will not sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information provided to us online with others without first letting you know and offering you a choice. See Ability to Opt-Out for additional information.
How we ensure the accuracy of the information…
VPI strives to keep your personally identifiable information accurate. We commit to responding promptly to any question about the accuracy of information from our customers. You may make a request to VPI for access to the information VPI maintains in its database, and review this information in order to correct, amend, or delete that information when it is inaccurate. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable measures to verify your identity before granting you access or enabling you to make corrections. This right only applies to personal information relating to the individual making the request and is subject to other limitations as defined by law. If you wish to make an access request, VPI's Privacy Advocate will explain the process to be followed. In order to confirm your identity and have the necessary information to retrieve your data, VPI provides a form which you fill out, sign and mail back to VPI. VPI does not charge any fee for the processing of reasonable requests. VPI agrees to process all reasonable requests within a reasonable time period, but reserves the right to deny access or limit access in cases where the burden or cost of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to the individual's privacy or in the case of a vexatious or fraudulent request. Requests should be submitted to: Video Products IncAttn: Privacy Advocate1275 Danner DrAurora, OH 44202Tel: 330-562-2622Toll Free: 800-626-7801 Email: privacy.advocate@vpi.us
Your ability to Opt-Out…
VPI will also provide you the opportunity to at any time let us know if you wish to opt-out of partial or all contact from VPI. This choice may be offered at the bottom of an online or offline communication from us, as well as on many of our web registration pages. If you have any difficulty exercising your choices, please send your request to privacy.advocate@vpi.us.
Oversight provisions…
VPI participates in the Council of Better Business Bureau's BBBOnLine Privacy Program. Two integral parts of the BBBOnLine program are a third party oversight function and a dispute resolution process. Further information about BBBOnLine is available at http://www.bbbonline.org.
Future use…
As VPI develops its business, there may be a change of control of Video Products Inc, or subsidiaries, affiliates or portions of VPI. In this situation, customer information is typically considered a transferable asset. Also, in the unlikely occurrence that Video Products Inc or a part of its divisions, affiliates or subsidiaries are purchased, customer information will be one of the transferred assets.
VPI reserves the right to make changes to our online privacy policy as business or technical needs require. In the future, should VPI decide to use the information that you provided in a substantially new way, we would notify you based on the email address you provided and offer you the opportunity to opt out of the new use. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, we would like to know so we can address them. Please contact the privacy.advocate@vpi.us or call 1-800-626-7801.
Products
Test Pattern Generators
CCTV Testers
LED Tester
Video Splitters
Cables & Adapters
VGA Cables
Standard VGA
